(Howard(arriving):)Raj, what are you doing here?
(Howard(arriving):)You were supposed to help me
pimp out my Vespa.
(Raj:)Are you under the impression
that we're still friends?
(Howard:)Ugh.
(Howard:)Come on, you're not still grinding
on the kite thing, are you?
(Raj:)It's not just the kite thing.
Every time we go someplace,
you dump me...
...whenever someone pretty comes
even though you don't have a shot.
(Howard:)I had a shot with that jogger.
(Raj:)Fine. Paint green flames
on your little scooter with her.
(Howard:)It's not a little scooter.
It's the second-biggest Vespa
they make!
You're watching football?
(Leonard:)There's no fooling you.
Now, what is this "sacks" statistic
they put up there?
(Howard:)All I know about Saks
is my mother shops there.
(Leonard:)Sacks, sacks.
(Sheldon:)It's football nomenclature
for when a quarterback...
(Sheldon:)...is tackled behind the line
of scrimmage.
(Leonard:)Huh.